Preliminary Guide to the Marvin Center Administrative Office records, 1948-2004 RG0052
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Marvin Center Administrative Office records
1948-2004
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
George Washington University. Cloyd Heck Marvin Center
RG0052
1.25 Linear Feet
The Marvin Center is The George Washington University's campus community center. This collection contains flyers, meeting minutes, brochures, buttons, newspaper clippings, correspondence, forms, memorandums, proposals, invitations, programs, post cards, newsletters, reports, a faculty planner, order forms, catalogs, booklist, invitations, flyers, schedules, mugs and cups.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Acquisition information is unknown for this accession
Historical or Biographical Note
The Marvin Center is The George Washington University's campus community center. It was opened in 1970, and named after former president Cloyd Heck Marvin. The Marvin Center offers programs, services, and facilities for students, faculty, staff, alumni, and University guests. The Center's wide range of facilities includes dining locations, a theatre, lounges, recreational facilities, study rooms, travel agency, computer store, GW Concierge, GW bookstore, Student Organization Resource Center, and conference and meeting rooms in the Morris and Gwendolyn Cafritz Foundation Conference Center.
The Marvin Center provides facilities for programs conducted by the University Program Board, by academic departments that include the performing arts, and by other University organizations. The operation of the Marvin Center is overseen by Senior Vice President of Student and Academic Support Services.
The Marvin Center Governing Board is a representative body composed of students, faculty, staff, and alumni. The Board works closely with the Center's staff in the review and development of policies, guidelines, and procedures that direct the operation of the Center.
The Director of the Center reports to the Senior Vice President for Student and Academic Support Services.
N.B. This history note was written in 2005
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains flyers, meeting minutes, brochures, buttons, newspaper clippings, correspondence, forms, memorandums, proposals, invitations, programs, post cards, newsletters, reports, a faculty planner, order forms, catalogs, booklist, invitations, flyers, schedules, mugs and cups. The records range in date from 1948 to 2004. The items concern the Dorthy Betts theater, exhibits, live performances, the Colonade Gallery, the governing board, the Program board, the building dedication, building plans, committee lists, films, other activities in the Marvin Center, the travel office, the University Bookstore, books for classes, and the student union that was formerly the Columbia Hotel. The mugs and cups commemorate special events.
Collection Organization
Organized into two series: Activities, events, and office files, and Mugs and cups.
Collection note
The only accession from this office transferred to the University Archives was recorded as missing from the collections in January 2002.
Bookstores; Conference rooms; Washington (D.C.); Foggy Bottom (Washington, D.C.); Dinners and dining; Theater; Travel agents; George Washington University
- Activities, events, and office files, 1948-2004; RG0052 Series 1; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2)
  Scope and Contents note
  This series contains flyers, meeting minutes, brochures, buttons, newspaper clippings, correspondence, forms, memorandums, proposals, invitations, programs, post cards, newsletters, reports, a faculty planner, order forms, catalogs, booklist, invitations, flyers, and schedules. They range in date from 1948 to 2004. The items concern the Dorthy Betts theater, exhibits, live performances, the Colonade Gallery, the governing board, the Program board, the building dedication, building plans, committee lists, films, other activities in the Marvin Center, the travel office, the University Bookstore, books for classes, and the student union that was formerly the Columbia Hotel.
  Formerly vertical files
  - Marvin Center, 06/1970 -01/2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Marvin Center - activities, 06/19/1970 -12/13/2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Marvin Center - Dorothy Betts Theater, 1975-04/1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Marvin Center - Dorothy Betts Theater - announcements, 05/10/1968 -05/01/2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Marvin Center - Dorothy Betts Theater - programs, 07/09/1970 -2004 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Marvin Center - exhibits, 04/04/1976 -06/24/1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Marvin Center - governing board, circa 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Marvin Center - history, 02/03/1971 -04/29/2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Marvin Center - history - 10th anniversary, 02/01/1980-02/16/1980 -- --ca. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Marvin Center - Information Desk, 11/01/1976 -05/1988 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Marvin Center - newsletter, 08/1977 -11/1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Marvin Center - program board [1/2], 1969 -04/25/1982 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Marvin Center - program board [2/2], 12/05/1969 -04/24/1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Marvin Center - program board - calendar/schedule of events, 10/07/1973 -10/09/1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Marvin Center - program board - film series, 1970 -04/12/1980 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Student union, 1948-1965 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Travel Office, 1972-1976 -- --ca. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - University Bookstore, 1964 -05/02/2002 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Mugs and cups, 1998; RG0052 Series 2; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series contains mugs and cups commemorating special events. Several of these items are dated 1998.
  Formerly ACC#1008
  - "Ski MC" mug, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Varsity Sport of the Mind" mug, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - "Marvin Gras, 1998" glass (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "Marvin's Beach-o-Rama" cup, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Riverside Cafe" mug, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Welcome Week 1998" plastic coffee cup (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - "Monumental Celebration at Union Station, 1998" (Commencement) candle holder (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Student org activities, applications, and building use, 1968-2013, RG0052 Series 3
  - GW Newspapers, April Fools Day, 1989-2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Governing Board, misc. documents, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - SORC - September MCGB Handout (copy master) includes Revised Proposal, Timeline and Hatchet Article, 1996-09 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Business Affairs Meeting - One Card Update (October '96), 1996-10 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Spring '97 Office Enhancements - Computer Proposals (2/97), 1997-02 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - October '96 & November '96, 1996-10-1996-11 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Agreement for Use of Student Office Space (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 2006-2007 Agreement for Use of Student Office Space (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Application for Marvin Center Student Organization Office Space, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The Gail Short Hanson Outstanding Service Award 1997 Nomination form (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Pompan (1/97) - January Finance Report, Elevator Case demo, SORC Q & A, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Appointments - Grad At Large (blank and filled) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - March Procedures (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1996-97 Appointments, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Finance Committee 1997 (2/97), 1997-02 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Agreement for Use of Student Office Space (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Application for Student Organization Office Space, 2007-2010 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Application for Marvin Center Student Organization Office Space, 2008-2010 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Agreement for Use of Student Office Space (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Marketing Group (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Marriott (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Board Meetings (Handouts (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bldg Services Committee (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Governing Board in Publications, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Conferences/Workshops (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Communications Committee (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Communications Committee - Fall 90-Spr 91 MCGB Brochure, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Communications Committee Fall 90-Spr 91, 21st Anniversary of MC, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Communications Committee Centerpiece Fall 90-Spr 91, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Communications Committe Fall 90-Spr 91, Signage, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Secretary Minutes - Summer 90 - Spr 91, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Secretary John D. Knadler, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Floor Plan - Project Outline, Summer Roster - Project List (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Committee on Health Promotion and Positive Lifestyles, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Governing Board, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Project 2000 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - ACU-I Nomatinations/Nominees, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - ACU-I 1990 Conference, Portland (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Governing Board letter (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - 1989/90 Nominations Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Shotokan Files, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Office of Campus Life Interdepartmental Memorandum, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - 1990 Office Allocations (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Men's Rooms, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - College Bowl Stuff for GWU (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Unity Week - Pizza, party, prose (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Marvin Gras - Feb 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Co-Sponsorships - 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Oscar Night - March 1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - George's Band Series (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Misc. Chair Reports etc (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Finance 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Budget Documentation & MC needs survey (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Scheduling Reservation Forms (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Office of Campus Life Reservation forms (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Sign-Up Sheets Committee Conferences Filled/Blank (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Opportunities 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - ACU-I, Nov 1993-Apr 1994, 1993-11-1994-04 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - VIVA - October 1993, 1993-10 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Menus-Food Service (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Excellence in Student Life MVM - Best Project Chair, 1994-02-28 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Gail Short Hanson Award (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Schedules 1994-1994, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Calendars - Spring, Fall (blank) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Leadership Team 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Newsletters, 1988-1989 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Stipend, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Memo: Marvin Center Building Use Policies, 1993-11-17 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - MCGB 1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - USU Alumni Club, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - JEC/Appointment, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Dining Services, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Dining Services Commission (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Dining Review @ Peer Institutions Fall 2005 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - 1997 Dining Services (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Joint Food Services 1979-80, 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Food Coop Survey - 1980 (spring) (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Food Co-op, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Governing Board Food Store (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Food Co-Op Proposal, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Meeting Agendas 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Marvin Center Governing Board, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - WRGW Proposal, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Personal Information Sheets, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Marvin Center Memorandums for Meeting Dates, 1996-09 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Student Organization Resource Center - Planning and Implementation, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - SORC, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Marvin Center Governing Board 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Secretarial Duties/Papers/Book, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Hatchet-Ads-Publicity (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Logos-Licensing (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Sigma Chi, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Marvin Center Governing Board (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Survey Administration - May 5, 1997, 1997-05-05 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Renovation Memo 3/7/97, 1997-03-07 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - MC 4th Floor 1996 Painting (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Finance Committee-December '96 & January '97, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Excellence in Student Life Awards, 1987-1997 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Space Allocation (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Marvin Center: Facility Use Summary (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - NACA Info (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Agenda & Minutes '91-'92, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Hanson Award, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Building Use 1990-1991, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Catering (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - MCGB/MC One Sheet Publicity 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Information Services 1997 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Letters to Stud Org, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - MCGB Questionnaire (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Open Projects, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - JEC: 96 Charter (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Leadership Team, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - SORC - Planning Meetings (Summer '96), 1996 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Student Organization: Planning and Implementation, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - SORC - Q & A History (Copy Master) used in mailer to student organizations in January '97, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Mailboxes (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Thanksgiving Lunch, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Ben To Do MCGB, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - MCGB Logo/Banner, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Logos, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Microwave/Commuter Lounge (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - SNS Issues, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Office Allocations, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Policy Revisions (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - JEC 2011 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - MCGB 2010-2011 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Elections (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Personal (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Student Advisory Council, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Cosponsorships April 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - MCGB 2009-2010 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - MCGB 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - MC Meeting Space (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - MCGB 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - MCGB 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Grad Publication, 2002-01 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Grand Reopening, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Finance Committee 97-98, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Co-Sponsorship Forms, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - O.B.U. Spring College Tour, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - MCGB Bldg Use, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Raffle License 11/9/01, 2002-11-09 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Financials, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - MC 418, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Applications (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Inventory (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Office Allocations, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - 1998-97 No. 1, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Meeting 1997-1998 No. 3 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Center Piece, 1990-04 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - CC Ball License, 2001-10-29 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Meter Bagging (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Carnival License - Consent, 2001-09 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - O.B.U. Tour, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Dove Spa 9/11/01, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Special Event Task Force (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Carnival License (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - MCGB Meeting No. 2, -2003 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - 98-99 Member Binder, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Diversity Program Clearinghouse 1997-1998 Annual Report (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Finance Program '98-'99, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - 1997-1998 Email Re: General Correspondence/Reorganization (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - 1997-98 Email Re: Room Usage, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - 1997-98 Email Re: Senate on TV, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - 1997-98 Email Re: Meeting Announcements & Meetings w/board members, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - 1998 Elections & SEC Charter Redrafting, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Email Re: Calendars, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - 1997-1998 Email Re: MC416 & computers (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Tab 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - MC Building Use Policies (c. 1996) from Handbook (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Tab 3 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Tab 5 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Tab 7 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - MCGB 1997-1998 Meeting Schedule (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Agenda & Minutes 97-98, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - MC Budget 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - JEC 2012 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Pending Projects (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Midnight Breakfast 2011 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Fall 2011 Tenut Meeting (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Spring 2012 Tenut Meeting (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - MCGB Meeting Minutes, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - MCGB Interdepartmental Memos (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Gov Board Block Booking 85-86, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Building Use Committee 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Blank worksheets for Function Groups (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - MCGB Meeting Agenda Aug-'86, 1986-08 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Memo ACU-I Nominating Committee, 1989-08-28 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Union Wire, 1988-07 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Business Affairs Task Force, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Posting & Solicitation - c. 1987 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 1985 Ground Floor Renovations (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Survey '90, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Marvin Center Security Info (1982) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Information Center C. 1980's, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Smoking Policy, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Posting Policy (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Table/Banner/Easel Space Policy, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - George's (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Post Office (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - G.B Proposed Reg for the Use of Outdoor Areas (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Disabled Student Access, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Employment (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Past President's ACU-I (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Greck Issues - c. 1988 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Misc. 1988 Files (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Governing Board Building Services, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Governing Board Finance Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Governing Board Communication Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Governing Board Director Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Governing Board Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Governing Board Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Building Use (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Budget Documentation for Fiscal 83; School Year 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Project Accts./Exp. Accts, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Prelim Budg. Meeting, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Buddy's Budget for M.C. Nov. 1981, 1981-1984 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Buddy Lesavoy, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Student Association-Joint Committee Information and Notes 1980, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Parking Study 1978, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Articles, Ads, Etc., 1979-04-05 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Governing Board Membership - GW, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Contracting for Services Association of College Unions - International Region 4 Conference, 1983-10 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - 1976 Budget Docs (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - PB/GovBoard (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Marvin Center Governing Board 1983-1984, Buddy Lesavoy (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - University Club Access (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Meeting Mtgs & Agendas, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - The Clyod Heck Marvin Center misc documents, 1979-1982 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Misc., 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Buddy / Marvin Center Budget for 1981-82, Preliminary Forecast for 1982-83, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Office Allocations 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Letters Concerning Womanspace - 1978 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Users Guides to MC. Facil 1979 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence - Boris Bell, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Past Meeting Minutes & Agenda Fall 1980 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Finance Rep, 1982-1984 (Box 4)
  - 1982, 1983 Doc (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Metamorphosis ACU-I Region 4 Conference, 1980-10-17-1980-10-19 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Marvin Center Budget documentation, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Governing Board '82-'83, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Marvin Center Comparative Income Statement, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Building Services Committee Fall 1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Governing Board Agenda, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Marvin Center Governing Board 1982-1983 Peter Repetti (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Financial Status of the Marvin Center as of June 30, 1984, 1984-06-30 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Budget notes (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - 2002-03 Elections, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Bulletin Board Apps, 2004-09-29 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - MCGb 2k3-2k4, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Room Confirmations, 2004-01-2004-04 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - MC 430 Computer Proposal, 2002-11-12 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - PK, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 2002-2003 Space Allocations MCGB, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Office Problems (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - MCGB 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Co-Sponsorship, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Retreat 10/5, 2002-09-2002-10 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Student Leader's Meeting - Proposed FY 2003 Budget, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Mail Account Slips (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Faculty/Staff vs. Students, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - University Budgetary Planning, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Responsible Alcohol Management Training Packet 2002-03, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - MC/SAC Publicity (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Office Supplies, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - MC General Info (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - 2002 Excellence in S.L. (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Marvin Center Activity Report & Other Docs, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Renovation Thank You Lunch, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - RHA-MC 423, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - JMM Reading Series-Sp 2003 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Office Health Safety Check, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - University Update/Tenant Mtg, 2003-02-13 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - 20-03 Member Binder info, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Election Night Party, 2003-02 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - MCGB Meeting #4 Oct. 24, 2004, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - MCGB Meeting #2 9/12/03, 2003-09-12 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - MCGB Meeting #3 Oct. 3, 2003, 2003-10-03 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Meeting #9 March 5, 2004, 2004-03-05 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Meeting #4 Oct. 24, 2003, 2003-10-24 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - MCGB Meeting #6 11/21/03, 2003-11-21 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Meeting #6 12/12/03, 2003-12-12 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Meeting #7 1/23/04, 2004-01-23 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Meeting 8 Feb. 13, 2004, 2004-02-13 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Website Draft (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - GWorld Copy Cards to be picked up (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Finance 02-03, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Greek Storage Space, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - AIESEC Allocation 4/02, 1998-10-12 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Key Signouts, 2001-05-29 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - GWorld CC Signouts, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - MC Evacuation Procedures (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Student Advisory Council (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Members (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Students/Student Groups, 2002-09-2002-10 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Financial/SASS Finan., 2002 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Administration, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Meeting #8 February 14, 2003 Marvin Center 405, 2003-02-14 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Meeting Space Confirmations, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Agenda Items-Meeting #` April 25, 2002 MC 403, 2002-04-25 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Meeting #2 Sept. 6, 2002 Morris Room 309, 2002-09-06 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Meeting #3 Sept. 20, 2002 Morris Room 309, 2002-09-20 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Meeting No. 4 October 18, 2002 Morris Room 309, 2002-10-18 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Meeting No. 5 Nov. 8, 2002 Morris Room 309, 2002-11-08 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Meeting #6 Dec. 6, 2002 Morris Room (MC 309), 2002-12-06 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Meeting #7 January 24, 2003 Marvin Center 405, 2003-01-24 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Meeting #9 march 7, 2003 Marvin Center 405, 2003-03-07 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Unidentified Documents (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Marvin Center Budget for 1984-1985 Preliminary Forecast for 1985-1986, 1984-1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Misc. 1984 Docs (Box 6, Folder 2)